{
    "id": "c904dd042da143398668994ca8436e31",
    "title": "General Grammar Exercise (Beginner)",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "We ............................... heard anything from them yet.",
            "description": "We use have before the third form of the verb.",
            "answers": [
                "aren't",
                "didn't",
                "haven't"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "61b376494aa94585a5defd7edc7751ac"
        },
        {
            "question": ".................................. you think we are doing the right thing?",
            "description": "We use do with you.",
            "answers": [
                "Do",
                "Does",
                "Have"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "d0c5c0a4fe3544a692c72cb05f50a7bc"
        },
        {
            "question": ".................................... you see him yesterday?",
            "description": "We use the simple past with past time expressions like yesterday. ",
            "answers": [
                "Did",
                "Have",
                "Do"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "f991ad5337c64133830e9ba293152744"
        },
        {
            "question": "................................... you free this evening?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Are",
                "Do",
                "Have"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "f8c5c67434e543589930fb44fa7c0850"
        },
        {
            "question": "How long ....................................... it take you to finish a project?",
            "description": "Does is used with the first form of the verb has is used with the third form.",
            "answers": [
                "do",
                "does",
                "has"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "6ddd2a0ac3db4a76bcc75d2044da97ed"
        },
        {
            "question": "She ...................................... rung back yet.",
            "description": "We use has/have/had with the third form of the verb. The past perfect is totally unnecessary here. ",
            "answers": [
                "didn't",
                "hasn't",
                "hadn't"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "e2b181842303424582456a5db7a3c637"
        },
        {
            "question": ".......................................... you call her in the morning?",
            "description": "We use did in the simple past. ",
            "answers": [
                "Did",
                "Have",
                "Do"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "eea7e181473d4407afd3c6075461d267"
        },
        {
            "question": "........................................ you play football when you were young?",
            "description": "Did is used with the first form of the verb. Have and had are used with the third form.",
            "answers": [
                "Did",
                "Have",
                "Had"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "26e62cea9dc046b98b35ea3432f78dde"
        },
        {
            "question": "........................................ you enjoy your stay here?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Do",
                "Have",
                "Has"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "0fbcbb455e484a16b0bae98cf32bb580"
        },
        {
            "question": "..................................... you enjoying this visit?",
            "description": "With ing forms we use are/is/am/was/were.",
            "answers": [
                "Do",
                "Are",
                "Have"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "b9036b5a86cb43b3a17c303d95c8701c"
        },
        {
            "question": ".................................. anybody here?",
            "description": "Anybody is used with a singular verb.",
            "answers": [
                "Is",
                "Are",
                "Have"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "322a84468fbf4140b1b2de1b00437fdb"
        },
        {
            "question": "Where ........................................ they live?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "have",
                "do",
                "does"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "70168e24bc6448be95312a3eee8fb2ae"
        }
    ]
}